We pray for hope and breathe curses and protect you from the dark
We're magical girls
We traded our souls for our powers and a destiny have battle
A destiny which ends in Oblivion for the only way to escape our despair
Is to vanish from this world
The end will come for all of us
So we continue our fight and wait for the law Cycles to lead us away
In this broken world
Doomed to repeat its tragedies and hatred I dreamt of someone I know
And saw her familiar smile again
It's morning already?
Good morning Kyubey
Good morning Dad
Hey Madoka
Morning
Mama yet?
Let's get waking her up.
You might need some help
What's new in your world
He told me that doing so well
Chucky been so busy it's hard for her to see him
It's going to be a big problem if they're serious about going steady
Keller don't get discouraged
Don't obsess
Here
Pictures of Tommy's in the dumps to
Talked about the end of the world in class all the time
Hellboy
Maybe I can set her up on a blind date
I wonder why she the more popular with the guy
A lot of really cute things about her
When it comes to Menchie's at their standards really high
She doesn't want to compromise
How she is
Here we go
We have a new student bring in today
That's weird isn't it kind of late in the year for that
What's the weather like
Whoever it is I hope we can be friends
VA safe
Now be good and eat it all up
Okay
Hey honey
Some more coffee
I better not
All right
I'm off to work
Have a great day
Hey you
He'll be late if you don't hurry
Glad you can make it today Modica nice job last night
You get me sleep after you got back I didn't have time to do the reading assignment though
Tell Steve I get called on today so don't even sweat it hell I didn't even bother doing my homework
Minecraft night more trouble
You hook me up with your homework later right now holding don't you dear miss Monica up in your feet
Because you won't let me see yours
Baby it's you I'm sneaking out by yourself and getting a head start on your homework
This is the beginning of the end
What's it all mean music by 2050
I don't know what you're talkin about male
41% of the population
Myblu any minute
The end of the world might not be such a bad thing
How much was man enough for one lifetime
The only thing I have to look forward to is hitting 40
Feathered all ended in one big
Mail
I'm going to have a new student joining us the rest of the semester
What is space cadet
Miss Academy
You can come in
It's nice to meet you
My name is Homer Academy
The kitty was in the hospital for a while due to a heart condition
She's been away from school for so long
So that's okay
Do you know about her how come you didn't say anything. I'm sorry I didn't I kept it a secret
Because I thought it would be a fun surprise
I should have introduced myself to you last night last night
You mean you are waiting at the Rendezvous point with Mommy how come you didn't help us
She did as a matter of fact she helped us out a lot
She had the most amazing power
If she works at that still boosters prank 200. I'm not really that strong but I can back you up
I'm not very good at attacks so well you seem pretty cool to me
And with all the big shot nightmares we've been fighting lately we need the extra help I guess after last night you proved you got what
It takes to all with us if you want to join our team I'm OK with it thank you for the chance to prove myself
I'll do my best to help you fight the nightmares and keep everyone safe
I won't let you down
I'll do our best together Homura
Isn't it pretty
Can you believe it's already been a month since you showed up here now I can it's like the time is it
Feels like I've known you forever though
Hippie nice that the nightmare stayed away tonight and everyone could get a good night
If I tell you something
Not to laugh
You're here and I was talking like this
Feels like something I've wanted for a long time
It's weird cuz we're just talking
We're going to see each other at school tomorrow anyway
It's not weird
I feel that way too
Sitting here with you
Seems like something I've wanted for a long long time
I can't game
It's just me
Are you free to talk now
WhatsApp
Siri call you so late but
I was wondering if you were doing anything this Sunday
Do you have any
Plan
Sorry
Understand
Schedule
There's nothing you can do about it
I know how dedicated you are to hear music
That's what I love about you
I understand
Music means more than anything.
And that is what I love about
Drive
Fashion
Whatever
I don't eat anymore
Disappeared on my way
Baby
Oh no not again
Goodness Me
I always pay late nights at the enemy of beauty
Hey ain't that you told me she's a pink nightmare
I guess she's having a hard time with a boyfriend like Captain oblivious it doesn't surprise me
It sounds like someone sent them moving on
Maybe hijack it up to like experience
Sharp you're putting yourself in danger if you don't take this seriously
Yes ma'am
Where's Monica and hamura sorry to make you wait
Recycle
All right
Let's go to work ladies okay
Ariel
I care how you feel
But you got to come down
Nicely done now let's finish this
Big cake round cake right in front of me
Do you think this cake could be
Please I'm just a little over a fairy that pig Brown
Can I see now cuz the cake beef chuck no not me
I'm the juicy Apple in this story that big red
Pound cake love baby can't you see it's a cake Mommy
It's not me I am busy
Big big round cake is tumbling UC could the cake be
Camera not me I'm the pumpkin for please
Big round cake sweeter than sweet
No it's not me and the melon don't you see
Play some Alan it will bring you sweet dreams so why is it
He's so bitter of Lake Havasu City's dream is over
Play-Doh Plus
Combining our powers like that
Biker down with a breeze
There was a moment when I thought we were in trouble though
It's best not to get too overconfident
Why did he got to be such a wet
Blanket
Instead of preaching you should invite us over for tea and cake
Now that's what I'm talking about
When is your friend Kyoko now that's a great idea
Who wants to come over for a fresh mints
I'm running a little low on chamomile tea
But I think I might have just enough for one more pie
Chamomile tea
Or I could make some of the echinacea tea I got the other day
Do sour
Taste buds develop at the first grade
I know baby I didn't forget he'll get a special treats to
Why so quiet
Oh it's nothing I'm okay
And that'll battles are
Have they always been like that
Do you want to try some of my fried chicken
Thanks
What's the weather
Okay what do you want to talk about
Wondering
Have things
The little odd to you lately
I don't know what you mean I'd like how well that's
The thing
Everything just seems off I got no idea what you're saying
You feeling okay
I guess the reason I wanted to speak to you before anyone else was
You are the one who sings the most odd to me
Why would I mean is compared to the impression I have of you
Something about you seems different
It's like you're not the same person you used to be okay what are you trying to do here trying to pick a fight with me is that what this
Look where you living now
Spider-Man I'm crashing at scientist
You lose your memory all of a sudden and how long have you been at meet Aki Hara
I transferred in a little while before you did
When was that
I guess it was last year around
What did I do
Whatever why is it matter where did you live before you moved here
Katamino the next city over things have got pretty quiet there for me
So when mommy told me stuff was getting out of hand here I came over
Have you gone back to visit cuz Amino lately no thank you I don't got no reason to go back there
Hey Kiyoko
Would you do me a favor
Come to cut the minnow with me I just want to go see it that's all
The cities the same as you remember I promise we'll turn around and come back
The no no it's just me and not something else
I got no idea what your trip is girl
But whatever it is I don't think you're pulling my leg hair
Not you you're on the level
I am
Well the trip won't be for nothing
I know a good ramen shops
Buy me dinner and we're even
We got a deal or what
Dinners on me.
At the next stop will be in Pasadena City
Stop
Maybe we got on the wrong bus
No way
I'm sure we got on the one for cuz Amino station
Let's catch the next bus and go back
And let's make sure it's the right one
That's the right one no mistaken
What's your problem
The hell's going on
We should try Walking Dead
If we go back to that
Panama City
Was that Crossroad really this far back
No
Sorry we haven't reached it by now
Something's definitely wrong
Either we missed the crossroad which I highly doubt or something else is going on here
What does happening cuz it's some kind of trick to keep us from leaving me Turkey Hollow City
I don't think the answer is as simple as that
My Siri
Is that nothing exists beyond the city
Really
Kyogre
I'm sorry
Could you not tell the others for a little while
There's something I want to check first
Just to be sure
Are you crazy we have to tell the others
I think it will be safer if we pretend we haven't discovered anything
How to draw attention to ourselves now will be hunted down
This is a trap make no mistake got any idea what's going on
That's why I don't want you to do anything
For now let me handle that
Far as I can tell
One has trapped us is only playing with our perception
That was long as we play along we won't be in any danger
Fine whatever you say
Maybe my memories are screwed up but I think I get where you were coming from before
Elsa
It's weird like
I don't remember you being as tough as your acting right now
But it doesn't surprise me either
This you the tough are you feels right
Am I the only one who remembers
Casting a kind of trap before a self-contained illusion a man with no
I praise the Lord and let it stray
There's no doubt about it
Is a labyrinth
The ones who spread
Bear and disaster
It's the final form a magical girl take
And she's lost hope and given in despair
I remember how hard I fought to change a cruel destiny
A repeating time over and over again
Finally thanks to one girl her sacrifice broke the cycle of Hope and despair
But that the world should have been led to a New Order of Things
However
It seems we've all forgotten would happen or rather
We were made to
Someone is trying to replace their memories of what happened with false ones
Trapped air in the spa Suite Aki Hara City
Silly thing
Mind your manners at
Set the table or you're going to turn into cheese
So cute together
Best friend
Even there was baby
Tagging along and being adorable
Baby and I have been friends for a long
What time
I met her before anyone else
We've had lots of Adventures
Do you remember how baby came to
Stay with you
Or when you met her
Baby coupons
I was just curious
I'm not sure the exact day but it seems like ages ago
Back in those days
I was all alone the only magical girl and misaki heart City
The only one who comforted me and cheered me on
Was baby
Without baby in my life
I would have given up the
The fight long ago
She's right Mommy
You're much braver and stronger than that
Not really
I just act confident because that's what's expected of a senior magical girl
The thing is
Monica and sayaka I'm coming to the road now
We even have you and she'll go to back us up to
I never dreamed I'd had so many friends I could rely on
I don't have to push myself so hard anymore
How I have helped
Now now
The nightmares have gotten stronger recently
AC4 fighting am now than I did before his now he's got more girls on the team
I get to work with my friends and that's always fun
Well
Fighting nightmares is not supposed to be fun
Don't forget that
I know what you mean though
Things are better now
The kind of life I used to dream about that before I meant all of you
We are bound by Destiny account
Battling
Define any happiness in a life like this is incredible
I never imagined it would be this
Nani
May I trouble you for some more
Back in a bit
I have to boil some more water
I'm sorry
You can stop the charade now
I remember what you used
Hear that
I know what you really are
You altered our memories entrapped Us in this fake mitakihara City
You can deny it all you want
Baby
This is your doing
What do you want with that it's some kind of game to you
Is this how you have fun
Memories are so annoying
Soon as I get one back others come flooding in one after the other
I remember Mami tomoe and now she always troubles me
She would put on a strong front and go all out
She had stopped his heart of any of us
Revealing the truth is always hard with her there
Shattering her optimism
And it hurt me
I remember now and I wish I could erase the memory of all the hearts I broke
Why are you doing this
Tell me right now or I'll lend you
I was going to wait until I understood the situation but you were hurting baby and I will not stand by
I am let that happen
Yes
Explain yourself
Why do you want to hurt baby
You're being
This is not the real mitakihara City
Our memories are felons none of this is real
Really now Houma.
How can you feed this thing
Everyday Day friend
I suppose this means you're going
Going to protect that I'm giving you the chance to walk away
If you choose not to you'll have to fight me
We know each other's moves too well but if this rate do you think you can feed me I can Outlast
We aren't getting anywhere
Your magic is quite fearsome
But in a fight your fool if you think you'll always have the upper hand
Please Mommy
Can you tell something's wrong don't you feel anything strange about yourself
You could have killed me but you didn't that must mean you still have some regard for my well-being but
But still you were trying to kill baby
Please try to remember she's a witch the enemy of magical girl
I don't know what you're saying witches are not our enemies the race are
Free
That's what I've been fighting
What are these nightmares
What is this
What's going on
Who are you
Baby
People get mad about what I'm going to
Tell you
What are you doing
Honestly
Were you thinking taking on mommy when she's in top form
Couldn't help getting into a fight with
I was defending my
I was really after I day
Right
Let me guess
You thought cuz she used to be a witch she still that way
Jump to conclusions mat
Do you remember
Course I do
That's why I'm here
About it though
I mean why would a witch go to all the trouble of making a labyrinth big enough to hold the city if all she's going to do is keep us here
She's been trying to hurt us and she's not learning new victims in either
Do you remember wouldn't do that
It's not without the first chance you got when she
You would realize that if you stop to think
It's pretty obvious is Labyrinth supposed to sign the letter people in
The witch who made it wants to maintain the status quo in here
What's going on
Christmas who would want things to keep going on like this
NY
Start their work backwards and
Running back into your own little time again huh
That's a bad habit of yours
Tri-County electric too much
You think the person who trapped Us in here
Might be one of us right would it really be all that surprising if it was remember what Mommy said
About her life now
She said it's the happiest she's ever been so
You think she could be the one
Which is the final form of a magical girl
I don't know
Maybe she is maybe she hasn't
That sounds like something you'd say
Well I got you here mind if I ask you something
When you find the witch who made this Labyrinth
What you going to do with her homework
You're what killed her
Why cuz she's a witch
What are you getting at
Is it really so bad
I mean really
We don't have to kill anyone
You keep working together and having fun
Is the person who wished for a life like that so evil
But she deserves to die
All done
Are you siding with a witch
Like I said
They're what we become
Go figure I'd sympathizer
I just realized
Crucial Point novel
The creatures mommy remember site
Where rates not witches
And Kilgore didn't understand the concept of Lab Rats when I mention that
Not because they forgotten about witches
But because neither of them knew about them in the first
And switches don't exist in this universe
A magical girl soul is supposed to be taken by the law Cycles before she becomes a witch
That's a concept she created
When Shiva made the world
She sacrificed
I knew it
You remember her too don't you
Yes I do
And that's what bothers me
I should be the only one there are three people in this world
The first one is the which made the Labyrinth the second one is baby who looks
And the third one is you who remembers when
Come are you are you really play a comedian
Pokemon
I'm the same old site that you've always known
Transfer student
Your reflexes are impressive you certainly weren't this agile
Whatever you do next ask yourself this one question would you be okay
Destroying this version of Itachi Harbor City think hard about that before you do anything
Just so you don't regret it later
Insidious Bank
An idealized World someone dreamed up
Mommy needed help
Sitting so I came over
I used to dream about before I met out of you
Epic really feel bad I mean really
Stream world has turned her back on her responsibility to fight The Wraith
I can't forgive anyone who do something like that magical girl
Keep fighting always
The price we've paid for our wishes
Our Fate was tragic one but she gave up everything to change
The sparse is wasting the sacrifice mother-gone-mad Pratt
I won't allow it
For you
Tommy's worried about you you know that
I'm okay
Talk like that
Some things never bugging you you can always come talk to me if you want
I might not be able to help you much with your problems
But it's way better than having to worry about them all by yourself
Hurts me to see you suffering so much when all I want to do is help
She would talk to me
I had a dream
And it scared me
In my dream
He went someplace
Far away
Newest so far I wasn't going to be able to see you again
And everyone forgot about you
Remember do you except for me
Memories with you
You're right
That dream does sound awful
But it's okay now really I'm not going anywhere especially if it's so far away I couldn't see you
Again I never do something like that
You know how windy is it
If I did anything that makes someone as strong as you cry like this
It would break my heart
Break your heart
I could hurt you so much
Course it would
I hate to leave you in Saiga for Mommy and Kyoko or my mom
He told me in our friend's request to
I wouldn't go if I couldn't see you guys again
I know I don't have the courage to do something like that
Even if I didn't have a choice
I knew it would hurt you more than anything
Just stopped you back then
No matter what I have to do
I want you to know that when the time comes and you have to make a hard decision you will have the courage to
To find out there are things only you can do
Angel jets out strong
And how kind you really are
You probably don't remember anything either
I know there's a chance you might just be an illusion
Fake version of you someone created
How else could we see each other again like that
Stephen Mader
Tatsumi
I can tell you the real model
You're here and I can talk to you again and feel your kindness one more time
Thank you
Pint of ask her anything that would make me happier than I am right now
I have to go now
Sorry but there's something I have to do
Where are you going
I wonder what's going on with
Hey Homer what's going on
I was wondering do you remember
If I said I don't if that's something I should be worried about
You shouldn't remember them
What about Monica, do you remember her
I remember her
No
If things were in order you shouldn't remember her
Those memories are false
This is like some kind of bad joke
For real
If I stopped and thought about it from the start it would have
Creative worlds remodel Gazette someone would have
Know about Monica to begin with
I figured it out I know who rewrote our memories and Travis Miss false maitake
There's one last thing I have to confirm for sure don't worry I can do this by myself
And if I'm right I'll and everything I'm sorry I got you involved in this
There's a limit to the distance
Body can be away from my Soul Jam
HEB 100
Passengers down for the elementary school.
I'm not a magical girl anymore
How can it happen
I'm sure you didn't really want to know the truth
And yet you couldn't bear it if you didn't seek it out human curiosity is quite fascinating
And a logical considering you were the one searching
I was certain you'd uncover the truth eventually home that I Cami incubator
I should have known this could only be your doing
Naturally now correct me if I'm wrong but you're probably wondering where your body and soul are
Would you like to know permit me to show you
This is outside the first mitakihara city this is the real you
In the real world
We developed in isolation field to completely can
In your soul gem we were curious to see what happens to a tainted soul gem in a closed environment
It had to be free from all external influences for the experiment wouldn't work
What is it that cleanses match
Magical girls and make them finish it's something you called a lot of Cycles well we wanted
You know what happened to whistle Jam when it's cut off from this phenomenon thanks to you we witnessed some very interesting
We observe the peculiar clothes face when they could shape its own reality as well as
Lauren trap victim now correct me if I'm wrong
But I believe this is the power of that which concept you think twice before
Your soul gem remains intact preserve buddy isolation field it's the old
Only thing keeping you from completing your transformation into a witch excuse the metaphor but you're like a chick that
It wasn't able to break out of it's shell and matured inside it that's the reason you end up creating a labyrinth
Charlie as opposed to externally under these conditions you managed to recreate a whole city inside York
Shell in other words
This is the world inside your soul gem
Interesting Theory
But it does Labrinth is isolated from the world how could anyone be lured into it it's not possible
True
But we need a little adjustment
The isolation field barrier only works in One Direction
Even though what repels interference from the outside we can allow victim to pass through but
Only if they're invited from within and you did the inviting you unconsciously chose your target
Once you let them enter they were trapped even under these limited conditions
We surmised refer to what the law of Cycles ever wanted to reach you it good
All they had to happen with for you to invite against your labyrinth then it would materialize in the form of one of your car
Target one strap we incubators would finally be able to identify and observe it
Then we could find out what this karmic force is that makes magical girls disappear there are several people
Exist in the real world and yet they seem to have existed at some point in time
The most interesting of these is a girl who isn't recorded in any past memory and who was into future
Possibility either even though she doesn't exist with
In the karmic cycles of our universe she was able to slip into your world without causing any disturbance
We were fortunate we didn't have to spend too much time or energy searching for it who knows how long.
That was taken but you saved us the trouble home and I Cami thanks to you referring to the law of Psych
Smart economy
If we were disappointed in anything it would be that mad economy never displayed any sign of
Having unusual power it seems to memory rewriting performed by you the master of the labyrinth
Affected her as well she not only forgot the reason she entered
To save you
She also lost sight of who she really was and her capabilities
So we couldn't do anything to her
On one hand madoka kaname forgot she was a God and
The other you forgot you were a witch because of that we incubators could only watch as this point
Listen Deborah on folded we were fine waiting patiently in observing but since you discovered the truth
The delicate balance within your world has started to crumble
Reach out to Mark economy for help if you do that it will make her remember who she really is
And what you came here to do tell me what your real goal is incubator
Of course the law of Cycles has been a hypothesis up to this point now we can observe it
For what purpose
Satisfying curiosity is illogical
You said so yourself so I can't believe you go to such lengths just to confirm modify exist
I won't deny it
With our end goal in this whole Affair it would have been a long and difficult Endeavor though after all
The phenomenon has been a complete mystery to us we can't very well interfere with something when we can confirm
True
If we could we could interfere with it and if we can interfere with it we can control it the
Can we collect from that would allow us to conquer the law of Cycles completely then we could make a magical girls
Turn into witches energy all-in-one go your hope and despair are the key
The phase change between those emotion creates huge amounts of energy
You magical girls at the Gateway to Limitless possibility in our humble opinion
You should all conclude Your Existence by transforming into witches
Why are you angry because nothing to do with you anymore Your Existence has reached its completion
And now at the end of your life you could change your wish to meet the one person you waited so long for it
I should think you'd be happy about that hardly I have anything
You can't be serious you're creating a Curt what are you thinking it's running too fast for purified
As you are now he won't know that but you said the reason I chose
Become a magical girl lets it save Mother God
You want me to betray her but I'd rather turn
12 weeks before I get you and I will never let you incubator touch her again
You willing to give up your salvation for her
If you do you'll spend the rest of Eternity living among all these curtain not at all
In fact I'll make sure that the Labyrinth will be my grave Mami tomoe in Yokosuka
What are both here I have faith in them
Have any idea what it would mean if you died inside the isolation field you won't be able to break out of the shell
New transforming pool which inside a day if you're trapped in there's a lot of Cycles won't since you will be destroyed
And your soul no one will be able to save it from despair you lose your chance to see my tackle tournament again
You can't want that would you shut up already
I can't believe you prefer the worst possible face
Honestly I can't comprehend why human thought is so illogical
So that is being a witch
My emotions have all come back to haunt me again
I can't run
Amber anything anymore just glimmers of light and Rick Ross
Yes
My despair
I just want to say thank you for coming here
I can't even say goodbye
A witch
You don't have to be scared of her she looks horrible but she's the one who's suffering here
It's like a bad joke
Wait a moment
Really going to fight your friends are you
UK
I had no idea you could talk
It's unfortunate QB
But we have to trust with babies told us
Model Collison
You have the power to save her
All you have to do is acknowledge the real power inside you
Don't listen to a Monica
It'll be fine
You'll see just what I told you earlier
It's okay Houma. We're not going to let you go on like this
Promise
What are you buy a gun I one spot help
The world we succumb to Despair and sweater Christmas thanks a lot cycle me and her
Are working to free the world in that text me once and for all
You are so focused on you never noticed that
Where was the only way we could work without you interfering
The two of you are actually part of the log cycle no not exactly
Make her private secretary job with a hang on to all of Monica's memories and Howard
I saw this backup and she's mine it seems my better one of us didn't make it there
It'll be someone to return Monica's Memory Care
Finding the three of us in here to say informative play Overkill to me
Naruto's back for sure
Yeah but it's for her real good so it's worth the trip besides she fought hard
Keep the world safe to Stephen Hurd the least we can do
Can I modify
It's time we got to work
Pomodoro
Quit being so stubborn. Already
Man what the hell do you guys got me into
Marigot thanks a lot I had a horrible dream about you last night
You were dead
But it wasn't a dream it was real wasn't this right here
Fighting side-by-side
This is the dream
It'd be sad if it were but it's not like that not really
I thought I didn't have any regrets when I died but the truth is when I found
Mad about this assignment I jumped at the chance to come back cuz in the end
I did have one regret you I miss you
Looking back if I want to see one more time thanks a lot
Kill the mood
Wesley backpack feel open you'll be free if the incubators don't have a hold on you you can reach the outside
I want to see the real magic again
I told you
You shouldn't go off by yourself
Whatever happened to you good or bad you're still you and I would never abandon you
So don't give up
Long as I could have you back
Titanic together
You ready
You're not scared are you
I'm fine
I'm not afraid
I'm ready
Talking baby
They're gone just like that
Not yet
They're helping Monica take home or away
Is that
Madoka kaname
She's the love Cycles in one day
She'll take us to
I remember the reason I'm here to get home at
Can't believe I forget something
They have some unnecessary interference
What a trip
Talk about spinning are real that was kind of annoying
He waited for me all the time
I'm sorry it took so long but I'm here now
X + 1
And now I'm we'll be together
Until know how long
I've waited
I got you
Hypnotic art
I don't expect you to understand no one in the world could possibly understand
Piximotion is mine and mine alone and I've been saving it for her
It has to be this way
I'm never going to let you go again...
The world is being Rewritten
Is this mean a new principal has been born into this universe
You don't remember the last time this happened to you
What is the second timer
What's happening
Academy
What are you meddling in
You're changing something but what
I don't believe it
You're tainted soul gem should have disappeared with your soul
What happened
Why
Because
I remembered why I repeated time
Over and over again
They run so deep even pain has become precious to me
What is
Something you can't understand
It is the Pinnacle of all human emotion
Then what are you you're not a magical girl
Anymore but you're not transforming into a witch either
I'm not a magical girl or a boy
And I told her from heaven so if you want to know
If anything you can call me it's even now
There's no doubt now trying to put human emotions to use is just too dangerous for us
We could never hope to control something whose final form is so irrational is that so
The tractors that are spread across our world
Incubator
You're going to die
And you babe
Hey
Do you have any idea what you
Done
I do
But if you'd like to share your thoughts
Please
Enlighten me
Okay
You broke off a piece of a lot cycle
Hippie only salvation of magical girls had
I only took a tiny sliver of
That's all
The piece that used to be Monica
Before she cease to exist
For some reason you were all pulled in with her
And now you can't return to where you came from either
You have no right to screw everything up like this
I'm inexistent call the evil now
And if evil is supposed to distract the Divine and be a force of Chaos
It's only natural for me to accept the loss of a god
Oh yeah
What are you doing next story everything
After other race have been wiped out perhaps I will
When that day come I suppose I can be your enemy then
The question is will you be able to stand up against me
You're having a hard time remembering things aren't you
I think I remember being part of something
Some kind of being
What power bigger than this world
I can't remember what it was anymore
All I know is I'm not supposed to be here
You're getting another chance at being human again
If anything you should be happy about that
Eventually life here will seem natural to you
And you'll forget all about the path
She going to fight you
There's one thing I won't forget
You, that Kelly
Demon
We should pretend to be on good terms
If you're always attacking me
Monica might end up hating you
How you doing
Good morning psychic sleep well
Yeah
Hey guys
How's it going
Are you okay sorry
I don't know I guess when I saw you guys
And heard people say good morning again
Super happy
Battle
How do you say the most mysterious things
Yep that's the original International
Welcome to our new classmate
Anime
Come on Inn
Do we have to move there
Another word back he'll be starting school here today
Keep it out of the country for so long
Adjusting
Hey I was wondering
America
What's a cool over there I bet it was huh I wish I could go
You guys
Can't you see you're making her nervous bombarding her with questions
Why don't you give her a mon
Oh yeah
I'm hungry but I can't
Nice to meet you
Academy
May I call you mother pants
If you don't mind
I'd like to show you the campus now
Follow me please
Tell me how much
Showing me around
How does it feel to be back in
Everything feels familiar
Epistane timer
Strange
I'm not surprised it's been 3 years
Feels like nothing's changed at all
In fact
Everything's changed around here it's me
Hit me should have a different form different
It's okay
Exactly what you should be
Madoka kaname
You treasure the world you live in
Would you break it the law to follow your heart
To treasure this world
But I don't think a person to go and break the rules
Because they feel like it
Well then
Supposed
You will also be my enemy
I don't care
I'll keep wishing for a world where you can be happy
I knew it
They always did look better on you
The weather